blackvue.com 2019-06-02

# BlackVue Warranty, Terms and Conditions

**Privacy Policy for blackvue.com**

 **Effective date: May** **25** **, 2018  
Previous version available under the “Archives” tab.  
**

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. (“ **us** “, “ **we** “, or “ **our** “) operates the [www.blackvue.com](https://www.blackvue.com/) website (the “ **Service** “).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

 **Table of Contents**

  * Definitions
  * When do we collect information?
  * Information Collection and Use
  * Use of Data
  * How can I opt out or unsubscribe from receiving emails?
  * Retention of Data
  * Transfer of Data
  * Disclosure of Data
  * How do we protect your information?
  * Security of Data
  * “Do Not Track” Signals
  * Your Rights
  * Service Providers
  * Links to Other Sites
  * Children’s Privacy
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Contact Us

## Definitions

### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

### Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

### Data Processors (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

### Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

### User

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

## When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.

## Information Collection and Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“ **Personal Data** “). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Cookies and Usage Data

If you opt in, we may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device (“ **Usage Data** “).

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly. Our Online Store in particular may not function properly or be able to display your cart data if you disable cookies.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  *  **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service and help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  *  **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  *  **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

## Use of Data

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested
  * To quickly process your order
  * To send emails regarding your order
  * To respond to inquiries, requests or questions (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * If you opt in: To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

## How can I opt out or unsubscribe from receiving emails?

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving newsletters, special offers or marketing/promotional emails, you can:

  * Follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email we send; or
  * Email your unsubscribe request to [cs@pittasoft.com](mailto:cs@pittasoft.com)

and we will promptly honor your request.

## Retention of Data

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

## Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside of the Republic of Korea and choose to provide information to us, please note that we may transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the Republic of Korea and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure of Data

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Pittasoft Co., Ltd. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Pittasoft Co., Ltd.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## How do we protect your information?

First of all, our website is hosted by WP Engine, a Texas, US-based hosting provider. They implement a multitude of proactive measures against malicious attacks and their security is one of the best among hosting providers. Details about their security measures can be found here: https://wpengine.com/support/wp-engines-security-environment/

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider (PayPal) and are not stored or processed on our servers.

## Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## “Do Not Track” Signals

We do not support Do Not Track (“ **DNT** “). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

## Your Rights

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Pittasoft Co., Ltd.. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“ **Service Providers** “), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

 **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

### Behavioral Remarketing

Pittasoft Co., Ltd. uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

 **Google AdWords**

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise across the Internet, in particular on the Google Search and Display Networks. AdWords remarketing will display ads to you based on what parts of our website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your web browser. This cookie does not in any way identify you or give access to your computer or mobile device. The cookie is used to indicate to other websites that “This person visited a particular page, so show them ads relating to that page”. Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: https://adssettings.google.com/

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

**Facebook**

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA <https://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada <https://youradchoices.ca/> or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

 **PayPal**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

### Newsletters

If you opt to receive our email newsletter, we may use third-party Service Providers to facilitate our email newsletter mailing list.

The email marketing service we use is:

 **MailerLite**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.mailerlite.com/privacy-policy/>

## Links to Other Sites

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website. We do include links to our distributors’ websites and our Blog section may include links to other sites, in which case we do our best to label those links accordingly.

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children’s Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“ **Children** ” or “ **Child** ”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “ **effective date** ” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: [cs@pittasoft.com](mailto:cs@pittasoft.com)
  * By visiting this page on our website: [blackvue.com/contact-us/](https://www.blackvue.com/contact-us/)
  * By phone number: +1 (844) 694-4469 (USA/Canada Toll Free)
  * By mail: Pittasoft Co., Ltd., 7F, BYC HIGHCITY Building A 131, Gasan Digital1-ro, Geumcheon-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea, 08506
